by-art.com 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy

  * Logged IP Information
  * Cookies
  * Software registration
  * Advertisers
  * External links
  * Children
  * Policy changes and contact information

Privacy of our visitors and customers is very important for us. We treat any personal information by utmost care and strive to protect you from disclosing your personal details to other parties. We do not require any personal information at this web site. If you contact us by e-mail, we do not collect or share your e-mail addresses with third parties.

Logged IP Information.

IP adresses of visitors are automatically logged into server logs at our web server. We use this information periodically to obtain server load and demographical statistics.

Cookies.

Several java games at by-art.com set cookies to save the game state between sessions, so that you can continue the game next time where you have left it. We do not collect this information. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.

Google's use of the [DART](https://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 

You and other users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Software registration.

If you decide to register one of our screen savers, you will need to contact one of our registration partners, either Kagi or RegNow. Both are among the most trusted names in e-commerce and have strict privacy policies (see [privacy policy of RegNow](http://www.regnow.com/privacy.html), [privacy policy of Kagi](http://www2.kagi.com/purchase/purchase_privacy.html)). We do not collect purchase information received from Kagi and RegNow. We have no access to your credit card numbers. If the customer asks us for a lost registration number, we requiest it from the registrator company. If you contact us with a question, your e-mail address is used only to provide you with an answer. 

Advertisers.

We use Google to serve ads when you visit our website. Google may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used, [click here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). 

If you click on an advertised link, you will leave our site. Please check the corresponding privacy policy at advertised pages.

External links.

By-art.com contains original contents and a very few selected external links. Nevertheless, if you find that the linked sites propose unappropriate contents or do not respect visitor's privacy, please contact us and these links will be analyzed and removed.

Children.

By-art.com does not request or collect personal invormation from visitors of any age, especially from children. We do not provide links to sites with the contents that may be unsutable for children. We will not allow at our site any ads displaying or linking to such contents.

Policy changes. Contact information.

All changes to the by-art.com privacy policy will be posted here. This policy is dated 29 March 2009. If you have any questions about by-art.com and this privacy statement, please contact: admin@by-art.com
